pointdollars.com 2012-03-20

# Point Dollars - Privacy Policy

|  |  |  | 

Privacy Policy

> At  **Point Dollars** , we strive to develop innovative services to better serve our users. We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use  **Point Dollars's  **services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it. 
> 
> The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.

Data collection

> **Point Dollars**  collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, the date and time of your access and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.
> 
> Some of our services require you to register for an account.  **Point Dollars**  asks you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address, e-gold account and a password for your account) and we will use that information to provide the service. For certain services, such as our advertising programs, we may request credit card or other payment information, which we maintain in encrypted form on our server.

Cookies

> Upon your first visit to  **Point Dollars** , a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website.
> 
> We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us.  **Point Dollars**  does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people access our site.
> 
> Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some  **Point Dollars**  features or services may not function properly without cookies.

Information sharing

> We will not sell, disclose or lease our members personal information to any other entity, unless this information is required by a local Law Enforcement Agencies.

Changes to this Policy

> Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice on our News Page. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.

|  |  |   
---  
Total Members 

2566

Members Online 

16

Offers 

2149

Offers Value 

$713.28 & 36634.25 points
